https://groceryoutlet.com/legal/privacy

Introduction
Grocery Outlet Inc., doing business as Grocery Outlet Bargain Market (“Grocery Outlet” or “We”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. We understand that you care about how we collect, use, and share information. This Privacy Policy applies to Grocery Outlet and our websites, mobile applications, social media sites and handles, and emails we send, as well as the information we collect when you interact with us through other online services, social media, and email, or visit one of our locations or attend an event sponsored by us (collectively our “Services”).
This Privacy Policy explains:
the types of information we collect through our Services
how we use and protect that information
the types of information we may share with others and under what circumstances
the choices you have regarding our collection, use, and sharing practices
details regarding our use of third-party cookies and other tracking technologies
We also include specific disclosures for residents of California.
This Policy applies to any official Grocery Outlet web site or social media. It does not apply to non-Grocery Outlet websites and mobile applications; please review the privacy policies on those websites and applications directly to understand their privacy practices.
Information We Collect
Information you give us: Some of the Services may include features or services that permit you to enter contact information and other information about you. We collect and store any information you enter on our Services. This includes:
Contact and demographic information when registering to use our Services.
Payment information and associated contact information when engaging in a transaction on our site.
Email address information when subscribing to our email bulletins.
Any information or data you provide by interacting in our online forums and chatrooms, or by commenting on content posted on our Services. Please note that these comments are also visible to other users of our Services and may be visible to anyone else on the internet.
Information you provide when you complete a survey administered by us or a service provider acting on our behalf.
Information you provide when participating in a charity event or offering a donation.
Information you may submit to inquire about or apply for a job with us.
Information you provide when you participate in a contest or sweepstakes that we offer
or that one of our Independent Operators offer.
Information you may submit when you inquire about or apply for a job with us.
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and any contact
information provided.
Information We Collect Automatically: When you interact with the Services, certain information about your use of our Services is automatically collected. Much of this information is collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies, as well as through your web browser or device. This includes:
Details of your visits to our site and information generated in the course of using our site (including the timing, frequency and pattern of service use) including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, the resources that you access, and how you reached our site.
Details regarding the device you use to access our Services, including, but not limited to, your IP address, operating system and browser type.
Information about how you interact with our ads and newsletters, including whether you open or click links in any correspondence.
Information that you make available to us on a social media platform (such as by clicking on a social media icon linked from our Services), including your account ID or username and other information included in your posts.
Please see below for more information about how our automatic collection of information works.
Additional Information About Our Use of Tracking Technologies and Interest-Based Advertising
Grocery Outlet relies on partners to provide many features for our sites and services using data about your use of Grocery outlet and other sites. We use cookies for the following purposes:
Site Operations: Enabling features that are necessary for providing you the services on our site, such as identifying you as being signed in, tracking content views, remembering your preferences and the number of times you have been shown an advertisement.
Analytics: Allowing us to understand how our services are being used, track site performance, and make improvements.
Personalized Advertising: Delivering tailored advertising based on your preferences or interests across services and devices, and measuring the effectiveness of the ads.
Social Media: Enabling the sharing of content from our services through social networking and other sites.
Below is a list of these partners with links to more information about their use of your data and how to exercise your options regarding tracking.
Partner
Category
Further Information
Facebook
Personalized Advertising and Social Media
Data Policy
Yahoo and Exchange (Verizon)
Personalized Advertising
Privacy Center
Google
Analytics
How Google uses information from sites or apps that use our services
Twitter
Social Media
Privacy Policy
LinkedIn
Social Media
Privacy Hub
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to disable or reject cookies. If you delete your cookies or if you set your browser to decline cookies, some features of the Services may not be available, work, or work as designed. You may also be able to opt out of or block tracking by interacting directly with the third-parties who conduct tracking through our Services.
You can learn more about ad serving companies and the options available to limit their collection and use of your information by visiting the websites for the Network Advertising Initiative, the Digital Advertising Alliance, and the European Interactive Digital Advertising Initiative. Similarly, you can learn about your options to opt-out of mobile app tracking by certain advertising networks through your device settings and by resetting the advertiser ID on your Apple, Android, or other mobile device.
Please note that opting-out of advertising networks services does not mean that you will not receive advertising while using our Services or on other websites, nor will it prevent the receipt of interest-based advertising from third parties that do not participate in these programs. It will, however, exclude you from interest-based advertising conducted through participating networks, as provided by their policies and choice mechanisms. If you delete your cookies, you may also delete your opt-out preferences.
How We Use and Protect Your Information
We may use the information we collect from you for the following purposes:
To provide you with our products and services, including to take steps to enter into a contract for sale or for services, process payments, fulfill orders, and send service communications.
To enable additional features on our Services and to provide you with a personalized service.
Create custom audiences on social media sites.
To provide you with the best service and improve and grow our business, including understanding our customer base and purchasing trends and understanding the effectiveness of our marketing.
To detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be fraudulent or illegal, and to comply with legal requirements regarding the provision of products and services.
How We Secure the Information We Collect from or About You
We use a combination of physical, technical, and administrative safeguards to protect the information we collect through the Services. While we use these precautions to safeguard your information, we cannot guarantee the security of the networks, systems, servers, devices, and databases we operate or that are operated on our behalf. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on or concerning this Website.
Our Sharing of Your Information
Service Providers: We engage vendors to perform functions on our behalf such as: website, software, and data storage, content management, database management, technical integration, marketing automation, analytics, site optimization, conducting customer surveys, and payment processing. There are limited circumstances in which the service provider collects data directly from you when their privacy policies may also apply.
Social Media Platforms: Where you choose to interact with us through social media, your interaction with these programs typically allows the social media company to collect some information about you through digital cookies they place on your device and other tracking mechanisms. In some cases, the social media company may recognize you through its digital cookies even when you do not interact with their application. Please visit the social media companies’ respective privacy policies to better understand their data collection practices and controls they make available to you.
Third parties involved in advertising: We partner with third parties who assist us in serving advertising regarding the Services to others who may be interested in the Services. We also partner with third parties who use cookies to display interest-based advertising to you on the Services. These third parties may use tracking technologies on our website to collect or receive information from the Services and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. While Grocery Outlet will not share information that identifies you by name with unaffiliated third parties for their own uses, such third parties may, with sufficient data from other sources, be able to personally identify you.
Corporate Affiliates: We may share data with other members of our group of companies.
Additional Information About our Data Collection and Sharing Practices
Sharing of Aggregated Data: We may analyze aggregated, de-identified data and share these analyses at our discretion, including with marketing agencies, media agencies and analytics providers. These third parties will not be able to relate this data to identifiable individuals.
Combination of Information: We may combine information from the Services together and with other information we obtain from our business records. Additionally, information collected about you from a particular browser or device may be linked to information collected from another computer or device that we believe relates to you.
Personal Data Collected From You About Others: If you decide to invite others to the Site, we will collect your and the other person’s names, e-mail addresses, and/or phone numbers in order to send an e-mail or text message and follow up with the other person. You hereby agree that you will obtain the other person’s consent to this before giving us their personal data. You hereby agree not to send us the contact details of any legal minor. We will inform any other person you invite that you gave us his or her details in the invitation e-mail.
Change of Ownership or Corporate Organization: We may transfer to another entity or its affiliates or service providers some or all information about you in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, acquisition, sale of assets or any line of business, change in ownership control, or financing transaction. We cannot promise that an acquiring party or the merged entity will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this Policy.
Cross-border Transfer of Data: If you use our Services outside of the United States, you understand that we may collect, process, and store your personal information in the United States and other countries. The laws in the U.S. regarding personal information may be different from the laws of your state or country. Any such transfers will comply with safeguards as required by relevant law. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your data.
Our Practices Regarding Information Belonging to Children: The Services are intended for users age sixteen and older. Grocery Outlet does not knowingly collect information from children. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected information from anyone younger than the age of sixteen, we will delete that information.
Your Options and Rights
Please visit the “Preference Center Login” page to update your contact information or change how frequently you receive emails from us or the types of offers you receive.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email bulletin or email us at privacyrequest@cfgo.com and we will promptly remove you from all correspondence.
Your California Privacy Rights
Persons with disabilities may obtain this notice in alternative format upon request by contacting us at privacyrequest@cfgo.com or calling 1-800-669-6566.
California Shine the Light: Although we do not currently share your information for other companies’ direct marketing purposes, residents of the State of California have the right to request information from us regarding other companies to whom we have disclosed certain categories of information during the preceding year for the other companies’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please email privacyrequest@cfgo.com or write to us at:
Grocery Outlet Inc.
5650 Hollis Street
Emeryville, CA 94608
Phone: 1-800-669-6566
Email: privacyrequest@cfgo.com
California Consumer Privacy Act
The California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) provides California residents with rights to receive certain disclosures regarding the collection, use, and sharing of “Personal Information,” as well as rights to know/access, delete, and limit sharing of Personal Information. The CCPA defines “Personal Information” to mean “information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household.” Certain information we collect may be exempt from the CCPA because it is considered public information (i.e., it is made available by a government entity) or covered by a specific federal privacy law, such as the Gramm–Leach–Bliley Act, the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act, or the Fair Credit Reporting Act.
To the extent that we collect Personal Information that is subject to the CCPA, that information, our practices, and your rights are described below.
Right to Notice at Collection Regarding the Categories of Personal Information Collected
You have the right to receive notice of the categories of Personal Information we collect and the purposes for which those categories of Personal Information will be used. This notice should be provided at or before the time of collection. The categories we use to describe the information are those enumerated in the CCPA.
Personal Identifiers:
We collect your name, phone number, and email address and contact address when you create an account or complete a transaction. If you choose to create an account, you will also be asked to use your email address as a username, and we will assign one or more unique identifiers to your profile.
You provide us with payment information, which may be your credit card number or a bank account, when you complete a transaction.
We collect your Social Security number, Driver’s License number, or Passport number when you apply for employment with us.
We may collect medical information and health information about you if you submit a claim or incident report relating to one of our locations containing that information.
We collect your IP address automatically when you use our Services.
We collect your Device ID automatically when you use our Services.
Protected Classifications: No personal information in the Protected Classifications category is being collected with the following exceptions: We do collect citizenship status if you apply to work for us and service providers or third parties may collect information regarding your age and marital or family status when they provide marketing services to us.
Commercial Information: When you engage in transactions with us, we create records of goods or services purchased or considered, or purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
Biometric Information: We may collect your image on security cameras but do not otherwise collect information about your physiological, biological, or behavioral characteristics.
Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information: We collect information about your browsing history, search history, information regarding your interaction with websites, and applications or advertisements automatically when you utilize our Services.
Geolocation Data: As described above, we collect your IP address automatically when you use our Services. We may be able to determine your general location based on the IP address. We also collect your Geolocation data as provided by third parties or service providers to determine where our customers live in relation to our locations.
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information: We record your message if you contact us by telephone and leave a voicemail. We may also capture video or photographic images of you through security cameras if you visit one of our locations. We use this information to improve our customer service, train employees, investigate complaints and incidents, and maintain the security of our locations, personnel, and customers.
Professional or employment-related information: We collect information about your current employer and your employment history if you apply for a job. We use this information to evaluate your application.
Education information: We collect information about the institutions you have attended and the level of education you have attained if you apply for a job. We use this information to evaluate your application.
Inferences drawn to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences or characteristics: We may analyze your actual or likely preferences through a series of computer processes. On some occasions, we may add our observations to an internal profile that we use to improve our products and services, or to offer additional products and services to you.
We may use any of the categories of information listed above for other business or operational purposes compatible with the context in which the Personal Information was collected.
We may share any of the above-listed information with Service Providers, which are companies that we engage for business purposes to conduct activities on our behalf. Service Providers are restricted from using Personal Information for any purpose that is not related to our engagement. The categories of Service Providers with whom we share information and the services they provide are described in this Privacy Policy.
We also sell some information to third parties. To opt out of the sale of your information visit our Do Not Sell My Information page.
Right to Know About Personal Information Collected, Disclosed, or Sold.
You have the right to request that we disclose to you the Personal Information we collect, use, disclosure, or sell. In order to process your request to know/access your Personal Information or delete your Personal Information we may ask you to take additional steps to verify your request or identity.
Verification Procedures
In order to process your request to know about or delete personal information we collect, disclose, or sell, we must verify your request. We do this by:
Providing personal identifiers we can match against information we may have collected from you previously; and
Asking you to confirm your request using the email or telephone account stated in the request; and
If you have authorized someone else to make requests on your behalf, we require that you provide notarized statements confirming the identity and authority of that person.
Right to Know/Access Information
You have the right to request access to Personal Information collected about you and information regarding the source of that information, the purposes for which we collect it, and the third parties and service providers with whom we share it. To protect our customers’ Personal Information, we are required to verify your identify before we can act on your request.
Right to Request Deletion of Information
You have the right to request in certain circumstances that we delete any Personal Information that we have collected directly from you. To protect our customers’ Personal Information, we are required to verify your identity before we can act on your request. We may have a reason under the law why we do not have to comply with your request, or why we may comply with it in a more limited way than you anticipated. If we do, we will explain that to you in our response.
Right to Information Regarding Participation in Data Sharing for Financial Incentives
You have the right to be free from discrimination based on your exercise of your CCPA rights. We may run promotions from time to time whereby we incentivize a consumer to share certain pieces of information with us; for example, we offer a one-time discount if consumers sign up for our email marketing list and some of our stores may offer “enter to win” drawings for prizes. Participation in these incentives is voluntary, and you may opt out of the data sharing at any time.
Right to Opt Out of Sale of Personal Information to Third Parties
We also sell some personal information to third parties. A company may be considered a third party either because the purpose of sharing is not an enumerated business purpose under California law, or because our contract does not restrict them from using Personal Information for other purposes.
We sell the following information to third parties:
Personal Identifiers:
We provide your contact information to directory service providers and public safety authorities.
We provide your IP address and Device ID to our advertising partners, Corporate Affiliates, and business partners.
All personal information may be shared with our Corporate Affiliates.
We may also disclose information to other external parties who are not listed here when required by law or to protect our Company or other persons, as described in our Privacy Policy.
You have the right to opt out of any sale of your personal information to third parties. To exercise this right, please visit our “Do Not Sell My Information” webpage or call us at 1-800-669-6566.
Please note that your right to opt out does not apply to our sharing of personal information with service providers, who are parties we engage to perform a function on our behalf and are contractually obligated to use the personal information only for that function.
We may also disclose information to other entities who are not listed here when required by law or to protect our Company or other persons, as described in our Privacy Policy.
How to Submit a Request
You may submit a request to exercise your rights through one of two means:
By filling out a Consumer Data Request Form available here.
By calling us at 1-800-669-6566.
Authorized Agent. You may authorize another individual or a business registered with the California Secretary of State, called an authorized agent, to make requests on your behalf. We require that you and the individual complete notarized affidavits in order to verify the identity of the authorized agent and confirm that you have authorized them to act on your behalf. Parents of minor children may submit a birth of the child certificate in lieu of an affidavit, in order to make requests on the child’s behalf. Please see our required affidavits here.
Special Information for Nevada Residents
Residents of the State of Nevada have the right to opt out of the sale of certain pieces of their information to other companies who will sell or license their information to others. At this time, Grocery Outlet does not engage in such sales. If you are a Nevada resident and would like more information about our data sharing practices, please email privacyrequest@cfgo.com.
Changes to This Policy
We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will post any changes, and such changes will become effective when they are posted. Your continued use of our Services following the posting of any changes will mean you accept those changes.
For questions about our privacy practices, contact us at:
Grocery Outlet Inc.
5650 Hollis Street
Emeryville, CA 94608
1-800-669-6566
Email: privacyrequest@cfgo.com
Sign up!
×
Sign up for our emails and receive $3 Coupon!
Sign up modal - Email*
Sign up modal - First Name*Sign up modal - Zip Code*Sign up modal - Select a Store*Select a Store*Aberdeen - 2715 Pacific AvenueAirway Heights - 10831 W Sr 2 HighwayAlameda - 730 Buena Vista AvenueAlbany - 1950 14th Avenue SeAllentown - 4628 BroadwayAltadena - 2270 Lake Ave.Anderson - 1981 Highway 273Antioch - 1818 A StreetAntioch - 3160 Buchanan RdArlington - 123 East Burke Ave.Atascadero - 2100 El Camino RealAuburn - 102 Cross Street SeAuburn - 414 Grass Valley HwyAzusa - 355 N. Citrus AvenueBaker City - 297 Campbell StreetBakersfield - 11200 Brimhall RoadBakersfield - 6421 Ming AvenueBaldwin Park - 4249 Maine AvenueBeaverton - 1355 Nw 185th AvenueBeaverton - 8620 Sw Hall BoulevardBellevue - 15625 Ne 8th StreetBellingham - 1600 Ellis StreetBend - 694-b Se Third StreetBishop - 1320 North Main StreetBoise - 5544 W Fairview AvenueBoise - 6969 W Overland Rd.Bonney Lake - 18318 Sr 410 EBremerton - 3445 Wheaton WayBridle Trails - 6625 132nd Avenue NeBrookings - 16261 Hwy 101 S Suite #17Burbank - 1615 W. Verdugo AvenueBurien - 236 Sw 152nd StreetCaldwell - 4907 Cleveland Blvd.Camas - 3308 NE 3rd AvenueCarson City - 1831 North Carson StreetCave Junction - 330 S. Redwood HighwayChambersburg - 1695 Lincoln Way E, Ste 2Chehalis - 1369 Nw Louisiana AvenueChico - 2157 Pillsbury RoadChula Vista - 1340 3rd AvenueCitrus Heights - 6059 Greenback LaneClearlake - 14806 Olympic DriveCloverdale - 111 Treadway DriveClovis - 1848 Clovis AvenueCoatesville - 1851 E Lincoln HighwayCoeur D Alene - 410 W Neider AvenueColville - 980 S. Main StreetCompton - 2175 West Rosecrans AvenueConcord - 1840 Willow Pass RoadConcord - 5410 Ygnacio Valley RoadCoos Bay - 1385 Newmark AvenueCorvallis - 1755 Nw 9th Street Suite 110Costa Mesa - 1835 Newport BlvdCottage Grove - 200 Gateway BoulevardCrescent City - 1124 - 3rd StreetDallas - 258 W Ellendale AvenueDavis - 1800 E 8th Street Suite BDinuba - 667 N. Alta AvenueDowney - 8320 Firestone BlvdDuarte - 1322 Huntington DriveEast Wenatchee - 315 Valley Mall ParkwayEaston - 2451 Nazareth Road Suite 12El Cajon - 350 N 2nd StreetElk Grove - 8517 Bond RdEllensburg - 705 North Ruby StreetEnumclaw - 960 Roosevelt AvenueEscondido - 1516 E Valley ParkwayEugene - 2060 River RoadEureka - 625 Commercial StreetEverett - 5209 Evergreen WayEverett - 710 Se Everett Mall WayFairfield - 200 Travis BoulevardFallbrook - 1101 S. Main AvenueFederal Way - 32945 Pacific Hwy SFerndale - 1750 Labounty Dr., Unit 101Florence - 2066 Hywy 101Folsom - 671 East BidwellFortuna - 1085 S Fortuna BlvdFountain Valley - 18920 Brookhurst StreetFremont - 4949 Stevenson Blvd
Suite FFresno - 1825 E Ashlan AvenueFresno - 2820 Tulare StreetFresno - 3566 W Shaw AvenueFresno - 5175 E Belmont AvenueFullerton - 120 N. Raymond Ave.Gardnerville - 1329 Us Highway 395n, Ste.12-3Gilroy - 333 E 10th StreetGrants Pass - 350 Ne Agness AvenueGrass Valley - 616 Sutton WayGresham - 2925 NW Division StreetHanford - 410 West 7th StreetHanover - 1150 Carlisle StreetHappy Valley - 14800 Se Sunnyside RoadHarrisburg - 600 North Mountain RoadHayward - 22660 Vermont StreetHayward - 31049 Mission Blvd.Hayward - 426 West Harder RoadHemet - 1460-1470 East Florida AvenueHillsboro - 354 South First AvenueHines - 627 Hwy 20 N.Hollister - 550 Tres Pinos RoadHuntington Beach - 16672 Beach Blvd., Suite IImperial Beach - 881 Palm AvenueInglewood - 2810 W. Imperial HighwayIrvine - 4730 Barranca ParkwayIsland City - 11301 Island AvenueJackson - #9 No. State Highway 49-88Junction City - 94582 Highway 99 EastKenmore - 7800 Ne Bothell Way Suite 140Kennewick - 1325 West 4th AvenueKent - 23910 104th Avenue SeKent - 26104 Pacific Hwy SKing City - 15705 SW 116th AvenueKlamath Falls - 4333 S 6th StreetLa Habra - 2001 W Whittier BlvdLa Mirada - 15745 Imperial Highway,suite BLa Pine - 51420 Us-97, Suite 200La Puente - 520 Workman Mill RoadLacey - 8221 Martin Way ELake Elsinore - 29231 Central AvenueLake Forest - 22475 El Toro RoadLakeport - 1155 South Main StreetLakewood - 11011 Pacific Highway SwLakewood - 5615 Woodruff AvenueLancaster - 1951 Lincoln Highway EastLancaster - 2108 Spring Valley RoadLebanon - 2540 S Santiam HighwayLewiston - 117 Thain RoadLincoln City - 4157 NW Highway 101 Suite 101Livermore - 1320 Railroad AvenueLodi - 520 S. Cherokee Lane, Ste #102Lompoc - 316 E. Ocean AvenueLong Beach - 1340 E. 7th StreetLong Beach - 6436 East Spring StreetLongview - 920 Ocean Beach HwyLos Angeles - 1120 West 6th StreetLos Osos - 1130 Los Osos Valley RoadLynnwood - 19800 44th Avenue WMadera - 1930 W. Cleveland AvenueMadras - 1537 Sw Hwy 97Mammoth - 37 Old Mammoth RoadManheim - 703 Lancaster Road (rt 72)Manteca - 1391 E. Yosemite AvenueMaple Valley - 26525 Maple Valley Blk DiamondMarina - 215 Reservation RoadMarysville - 9620-b State AvenueMcKinleyville - 1581 Central AveMcMinnville - 568 NE Highway 99WMechanicsburg - 85 Gateway DriveMedford - 35 East Stewart AvenueMerced - 1125 West Main StreetMilpitas - 215 W Calaveras BoulevardMilwaukie - 15810 SE McLoughlin BoulevardModesto - 1800 Prescott RoadModesto - 832 Oakdale RoadMonroe - 405 Butler AvenueMoorpark - 425 Los Angeles Ave.Moses Lake - 1177 N Stratford RoadMount Vernon - 1333 Riverside DriveNapa - 1491 W. Imola AvenueNational City - 3446 Highland AvenueNew Cumberland - 110 Old York RdNew Holland - 685 West Main StreetNewark - 36601 Newark Boulevard Ste. 25Newberg - 1510 Portland RoadNewport - 721 N. Coast HwyNovato - 1535 South Novato BoulevardOak Harbor - 775 Ne Koetje StreetOakdale - 808 N Yosemite AvenueOakhurst - 40301 Junction DriveOakland - 2900 BroadwayOakley - 3110 Main StreetOceanside - 3508 College BoulevardOlympia - 2100 Harrison Avenue NwOmak - 918 Engh RdOntario - 2275 South Euclid AveOntario - 2670 Southwest 4th AvenueOrange - 1803 East Chapman AvenueOrangevale - 8835 Greenback LaneOregon City - 878 Molalla AvenueOrland - 1026 South StreetOroville - 1060 Oroville Dam Blvd. EOxnard - 920 N. Ventura RoadPacifica - 5550 Coast HighwayPalmyra - 66 N Londonderry Sq Ste 300Palo Alto - 3445 Alma StreetParadise - 6026 Clark Road Suite AParamount - 15719 Downey AvePasco - 5710 Road 68, Suite 103Paso Robles - 2800 Riverside Ave Ste 102Pendleton - 1810 Sw Court AvenuePetaluma - 80 E WashingtonPinole - 1460 Fitzgerald DrivePlacerville - 1426 BroadwayPleasant Hill - 1671 Contra Costa BoulevardPorterville - 50 W Olive AvePortland - 10721 Ne Sandy BlvdPortland - 12102 SE Division StreetPortland - 4420 NE Hancock StreetPortland - 7120 SE Flavel StreetPortland - 7741 N LombardPoway - 13345 Poway RoadPrineville - 1951 Ne 3rd StreetQuakertown - 70 N. West End BoulevardRainier - 215 West B StreetRancho Cordova - 2801 Zinfandel DriveReading - 3260 North 5th StreetRed Bluff - 388 South Main StreetRedding - 2235 Churn Creek RoadRedmond - 798 Nw 5th StRedwood City - 1833 Broadway StReno - 200 Lemmon Drive Suite 101Reno - 3800 S Kietzke Lane #130Renton - 2809 Ne Sunset BoulevardRialto - 1145 West Renaissance ParkwayRichmond - 12010 San Pablo AvenueRiverside - 3550 Madison StreetRocklin - 6652 Lonetree BoulevardRohnert Park - 6335 Commerce BoulevardRoseburg - 930 W Harvard AveRosemead - 9026 East Valley Blvd.Roseville - 424 Roseville SquareSacramento - 1630 W. El Camino AvenueSacramento - 1700 Capitol AvenueSacramento - 2308 Del Paso Blvd.Sacramento - 3431 Watt AvenueSacramento - 3615 Bradshaw Road, Suite ASacramento - 6419 Riverside BoulevardSacramento - 7923 E Stockton BoulevardSalem - 2879 Lancaster Drive NESalem - 299 D Street NESalinas - 1415 N Main StreetSan Diego - 1002 Market StreetSan Diego - 3948 W Point Loma BoulevardSan Diego - 4360 54th StreetSan Diego - 5185 Waring Road, Suite ASan Diego - 8145 Mira Mesa Blvd., Suite 3San Francisco - 1245 South Van Ness AvenueSan Francisco - 1390 Silver AvenueSan Francisco - 2630 Bayshore BoulevardSan Francisco - 6333 Geary BoulevardSan Gabriel - 7260 Rosemead Blvd.San Jose - 1665 Foxworthy AvenueSan Jose - 2300 Monterey HighwaySan Jose - 272 E Santa Clara StreetSan Jose - 3140 Williams RoadSan Jose - 331 North Capitol Ave Suite BSan Leandro - 2179 E 14th StreetSan Luis Obispo - 1314 Madonna RoadSan Marcos - 125 S Rancho Santa Fe RoadSan Pablo - 2079 23rd StreetSan Ysidro - 444 E San Ysidro Blvd.Sandy - 36701 Highway 26Santa Barbara - 2840 De La Vina StreetSanta Clara - 3520 Homestead RoadSanta Cruz - 120 Morrissey BlvdSanta Maria - 1948 South BroadwaySanta Rosa - 1116 4th StSantee - 9759 Mission Gorge Rd.Scappoose - 52115 Sw Chinook WaySeaside - 1523 Fremont BoulevardSeattle - 1126 Martin Luther King Jr WaySeattle - 11656 68th Avenue SSeattle - 13201 Aurora Avenue NSeattle - 1702 4th Avenue SSeattle - 3020 Ne 127th StreetSeattle - 8700 15th Avenue NwSequim - 1045 W. Washington StSharon Hill - 1130 Chester PikeShillington - 3 Parkside AvenueSilverdale - 9451 Silverdale Way NwSimi Valley - 2974 Cochran StreetSonora - 685 South Washington StreetSouth Lake Tahoe - 2358 Lake Tahoe BoulevardSouth San Francisco - 125 Hickey BoulevardSparks - 1300 Disc DriveSparks - 2020 Oddie BoulevardSpokane - 1617 West 3rd AvenueSpokane - 7810 N Division StreetSpokane Valley - 12115 E. Sprague Ave.Spring Valley - 9805 Campo Road Suite 110Springfield - 160 S 14th StStanwood - 26905 92nd Avenue N. W.Stayton - 1815 West Ida StreetStockton - 1060 N Wilson WayStockton - 6618 Pacific AveSun Valley - 8920 Glenoaks Blvd.Sunnyvale - 1180 N. Fair Oaks AvenueSusanville - 1616 Main StreetTacoma - 3510 S 56th StreetTacoma - 6425 6th AvenueThe Dalles - 1300 West 6th StreetTracy - 825 W 11th StreetTulare - 170 E. Cross AvenueTurlock - 1330 W. Main StreetTustin - 12932 Newport Ave., Suite 20Twin Falls - 2318 Addison Avenue EastUkiah - 1203 North State StreetUpland - 176 South Mountain AvenueVacaville - 130 Nut Tree ParkwayVallejo - 401 Marin StVallejo - 66 Admiral Callaghan LaneVancouver - 5800 NE Fourth Plain BlvdVancouver - 9915 Ne Hazel Dell AvenueVentura - 9372 Telephone RoadVisalia - 2323 S Mooney BoulevardWalla Walla - 910 South 9th AvenueWatsonville - 1000 Main StreetWeed - 268 Vista DriveWenatchee - 1616 North Wenatchee AvenueWest Sacramento - 845 Harbor BoulevardWestminster - 15412 Goldenwest StreetWhite City - 7571 Highway 62Whittier - 13301 Whittier BlvdWillits - 1718 S. Main StreetWinston - 151 Nw Douglas Blvd.Woodland - 1325 Lewis River RdWoodland - 1366 E. Main StreetWoodlyn - 1936 Mac Dade BoulevardYakima - 2109 S 1st StreetYork - 1244 Greensprings DriveYork - 1500 North George Street Ste13Yreka - 121 Montague RdYuba City - 1721 Colusa AvenueQuestions about privacy? See our Privacy Policy or call 1-800-669-6566CAPTCHANameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
